{"allRoundData":[{"name":"Spanish to English \"I\" form.","timeLimitInSeconds":60,"pointsAddedForCorrectAnswer":25,"questions":[{"questionText":"What is the English form of the verb \"abandono?\"","answers":[{"answerText":"Open","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Hug","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Leave Behind","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Absorb","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What is the English form of the verb \"abarco?\"","answers":[{"answerText":"Finish","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Encompass","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Bore","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Open","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What is the English form of the verb \"abordo?\"","answers":[{"answerText":"Board","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Abuse","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Absorb","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Leave Behind","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What is the English form of the verb \"abrazo?\"","answers":[{"answerText":"Absorb","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Abuse","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Finish","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Hug","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"What is the English form of the verb \"abro?\"","answers":[{"answerText":"Open","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Am Plentiful","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Encompass","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Board","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What is the English form of the verb \"absorbo?\"","answers":[{"answerText":"Encompass","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Absorb","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Abuse","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Is Plentiful","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What is the English form of the verb \"abundo?\"","answers":[{"answerText":"Board","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Abuse","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Is Plentiful","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Bore","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What is the English form of the verb \"aburro?\"","answers":[{"answerText":"Bore","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Absorb","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Abuse","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Finish","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What is the English form of the verb \"abuso?\"","answers":[{"answerText":"Absorb","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Abuse","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Am Plentiful","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Finish","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What is the English form of the verb \"Acabo?\"","answers":[{"answerText":"Finish","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Leave Behind","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"hug","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Bore","isCorrect":false}]}]}]}